No one has the courage to get
work done from me, except you people. Just
a few days ago I fulfilled a demand and
now comments started coming for that look. I
asked the tailor, brother, for how much will you make the same dress,
say 5000. Then mother opened her cupboard and
started making arrangements. I tied the
dupatta that you people liked on the old skirt, twisted it around the hair, took
out the blouse from the hostess's saree and wore it, it
looked similar. I wore it in the same
style as didi has done with the then
warrior makeup. According to the end look,
I want smoky and thick eyes
for which I am going to use Midnight Kajal
from Ready Saheb. What a matte finish came with just one swipe.
Moreover, it is non-transparent,
light weight and also water proof.  Yes,
sharpener also comes for free.  Eyes done,
lips done, chick done.  Now it is the turn of my hair
which I have not combed for the last three days because I want this
natural look.   To
eat something, you have to lose something.  I have heard it.
But I am getting so much hair done to create a look.
Bean bracelet earrings.
How much my hard work paid off.  Letts C.  If you
want Ammai Amma full video then comment.   If you
want to buy Kajal then details are given, go and
check bye.